var questions = [{
    "question": "Who was not afraid of 'Red, Yellow and Blue'?",
    "option1": "Mark Rothko",
    "option2": "Roy Lichtenstein",
    "option3": "Barnett Newman",
    "option4": "Robert Mangold",
    "answer": "3"
}, {
    "question": "... is not a master of the 'Clair-Obscur'.",
    "option1": "Michelangelo",
    "option2": "Tintoretto",
    "option3": "Caravaggio",
    "option4": "Fra Angelico",
    "answer": "4"
}, { 
    "question": "Rem Koolhaas did not design ...",
    "option1": "Seagram Building",
    "option2": "De Rotterdam",
    "option3": "Seattle Central Library",
    "option4": "CCTV Headquarters",
    "answer": "3"
}, { 
    "question": "'Cicciolina' was the 'muze' of ...",
    "option1": "Keith Haring",
    "option2": "Damien Hirst",
    "option3": "Jeff Koons",
    "option4": "Andy Warhol",
    "answer": "3"
}, { 
    "question": "The Hermitage Museum started with the collection of ... ",
    "option1": "Marie Antoinette",
    "option2": "Catherine the Great",
    "option3": "Elizabeth Kortright",
    "option4": "Yekaterina Vorontsova",
    "answer": "2"
}, {
    "question": "Niki de Saint Phalle is widely known for her ...",
    "option1": "Donna's",
    "option2": "Doni's",
    "option3": "Nana's",
    "option4": "Maria's",
    "answer": "3"
}, {
    "question": "The initiator for a style called 'De Ploeg' was ...",
	"option1": "Jan van der Zee",
	"option2": "Hendrik Werkman",
	"option3": "George Martens",
	"option4": "Jan Altink",
	"answer": "4"
}, {
	"question": "Which chinese artist and activist was put in jail?",
	"option1": "Han Yajuan",
	"option2": "Ai Weiwei",
	"option3": "Zhan Wang",
	"option4": "Li Wei ",
	"answer": "2"
}, {
	"question": "... invited visitors to take the seat across from her.",
	"option1": "Heather Sheehan",
	"option2": "Anya Liftig",
	"option3": "Marina Abramovic",
	"option4": "Anastasia Klose",
	"answer": "3"
}, {
	"question": "The Khalifa Tower is designed by ...",
	"option1": "Cesar Pelli",
	"option2": "I.M. Pei",
	"option3": "Adrian Smith",
	"option4": "John Graham",
	"answer": "3"
}];    